(Penny:)It's just so weird.
(Penny:)Howard Wolowitz
is my friend.
(Penny:)You know, once he tried to
stick his tongue down my throat
(Penny:)and I broke his nose.
(Priya:)That's a little easier
to believe
(Priya:)than he's your friend.
(Penny:)Yeah, tell me about it.
(Priya:)You know, my brother had a group
of friends like this in India.
(Priya:)They dressed up in leotards and
goggles and called themselves
(Priya:)the New Delhi
Power Rangers.
(Penny:)You mean when
he was little.
(Priya:)Not as little as
you'd want him to be.
(Mrs Wolowitz:)You know,
this stuff is horrible.
(Penny:)You want to see if we
can find the cafeteria
(Penny:)and get real coffee?
Sure.
(Priya:)We're going to the cafeteria
to get some coffee.
(Priya:)You want anything?
(Leonard:)I'm fine.
(Leonard:)That's nice that
they're getting along.
(Raj:)Your girlfriend and your
ex-girlfriend are hanging out together?
(Raj:)Oh, yeah, that can
only be good for you.
(Leonard:)What are you talking about?
(Raj:)One of them
broke up with you.
(Raj:)Do you really want her
telling the other one why?
(Leonard:)I don't care.
(Leonard:)I don't have
anything to hide.
(Raj:)Good, good.